http://www.carterproducts.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Menu
Company
About Us
Events
Technology ProductsZ-Laser Pattern ProjectorsLine Lasers for Alignment and PositioningZ-Laser, Diode Laser & Guide Line LaserSeries M18 LasersSeries
M12 LasersRunner Series LasersZA Series Cableless LasersHelium Neon Line LaserDiode Laser Mounting BracketsINSPECTO-LIGHT™ Inspection LightingVacuum Clamping Flip-Pod®Flip-Pod® Vacuum Clamp KitsFlip-Pod® Vacuum Clamp ComponentsSanding AccessoriesSnap GaugeWide belt sanding Diagnostic DevicesBand Saw ProductsBand Saw Guide Upgrade KitsBand Saw Stabilizer®AccuRight® Circle Cutter and Center Master™ Magfence® II Band Saw Fence & F.A.S.T.™ AccuRight® Log Mill™ and Miter Mill™Band Saw Tires & WheelsStretch on Rubber TiresCarter ULTRA BLUE™ Urethane TiresRubber Tire AdhesiveRigid Wheels & TiresBand Saw BladesGreen Wood Saw BladesBand Saw Table InsertsBand Saw Blade TensionBand Saw GuidesGuide Upgrade Kits2300 Micro-Adjust Guide2400Guidall 400 Block ModelsGuidall 400 Roller Bearing ModelsGuidall 500Guidall 600 Block ModelsGuidall 600 Roller Bearing ModelsMicro-Precision model 10Micro-Precision model 20Micro-Precision model 30Band Saw Guide MountsEccentric StudsOffset StudsOffset Stud & Post BracketsSlotted BracketsSpecial Lower BracketStraight StudsBandsaw Guide PartsMicro Precision SeriesGuidall Series2000 Series Guides2300 Band Saw Guide Parts2400 Band Saw Guide PartsBand Saw AccessoriesWoodworking Video DVD'sWoodworking BooksTurning Tools and AccessoriesThe AXE™ Woodturning ToolsHollow Roller® Lathe Hollowing SystemsLathe MultiRest™ Work Support SystemPerfect Sphere™ ToolFACE-OFF™ Lathe Blank Faceplate MountsCenter Master™ Blank Creation SystemLathe Tool Handles & ColletsStrongbore™ Modular Boring SystemWoodturning VideosToolsMeasuring Tools
Service & Support
Document Library
Warranty Information
Terms & Conditions
Contact Us
Account
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is critically important to us.
Carter Products is located at:
Carter Products2871 Northridge Drive, NW Grand Rapids 49544 - MI , United States18886227837
It is Carter Products's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to https://www.carterproducts.com (hereinafter, "us", "we", or "https://www.carterproducts.com"). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Carter Products collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Carter Products's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Carter Products's visitors use its website. From time to time, Carter Products may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Carter Products also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://www.carterproducts.com blog posts. Carter Products only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Carter Products's websites choose to interact with Carter Products in ways that require Carter Products to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Carter Products gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at https://carterproducts.com to provide a username and email address.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Links To External Sites
Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.
Aggregated Statistics
Carter Products may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Carter Products may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Carter Products does not disclose your personally-identifying information.
Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, Carter Products uses "Cookies", similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Carter Products uses cookies to help Carter Products identify and track visitors, their usage of https://carterproducts.com, and their website access preferences. Carter Products visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Carter Products's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Carter Products's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Carter Products's use of cookies.
E-commerce
Those who engage in transactions with Carter Products – by purchasing Carter Products's services or products, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Carter Products collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Carter Products. Carter Products does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Carter Products may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Carter Products's sole discretion. Carter Products encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Carter Products Privacy Policy
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email or phone.
